Rogelio Herrera

Computer Programming

Phone: (347) 933-9643

Email: rogeliohc93@gmail.com

Key skills

Team-oriented

Written and verbal communication

Time management

Programming proficiency

Multi-tasking

Customer Service

Computer proficiently

BRM/CRM (Salesforce)

MS Office

Languages

Spanish (Bilingual)

Programming languages

C++ JavaScript

HTML Photoshop

Python

Summary

Computer Programmer and Graphic Designer bringing at least 3+ years of experience delivering error-free code within stringent deadlines. Comfortable with Agile frameworks and working collaboratively or autonomously. Skilled programmer and complex problem-solver. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude.

Experience

Graphic Designer/ Programmer January 2019 - April 2020 Emerald Immigration Center | Woodside, United States

- Update organization's website with upcoming events/news. Proficient with Salesforce for various clients.
- Provides maintenance and support to organization's website and main portals.
- Helped to collaborate ideas for websites, logos, business cards, created and sent invoices to clients using Salesforce.

Web Designer April 2018 - September 2018 EGT Networks Inc. | Brooklyn, United States

- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including ecommerce capability, security and specialized scripts.
- Designed user interface and integrated into content management system to meet client specifications.
- Performed technical presentations for internal colleagues and external stakeholders to illustrate proposed site designs.

Computer Programmer

April 2015 - July 2017

BH Company | Brooklyn, United States

- Consulted regularly with internal customers on application development project status, new project proposals and software-related technical issues.
- Built, tested and deployed scalable, highly available and modular software products.
- Researched, designed and implemented scalable applications for data extraction, analysis, retrieval and indexing.

Education

ASA College | Brooklyn, NY
Associates in Computer Programming

June 2018

John Jay (CUNY) | Manhattan, NY Bachelors in Computer Science

Expected Graduation Fall 2022